# Kasia Mirowska

# Full Stack Web Developer Boston, MA

781 307 6258 | amirokasia@gmail.com in/kasiamirowska | github | portfolio

### **SUMMARY**

Javascript Web Developer experienced in designing, developing, testing, debugging mobile and web applications. Experienced small business owner, taking ownership of my work and a natural leader. Developed dynamic, interactive applications using React, React Hooks, Node, Express with Restful API and SQL database.

## **SKILLS**

FRONT\_END: Javascript, React & React.Context, Redux, Hooks, Sass, Styled Components, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, BACK\_END: Node.js, Express, Knex, SQL & PostgreSQL, Firebase, TESTING: Jest, Enzyme, Mocha, OTHER: Git & Github, Zeit, Heroku, NPM, Photoshop, Illustrator

#### **PROJECTS**

# Crown-Clothing | Demo, Github

An e-commerce web application featuring a full online clothing store with google sign-in and payment processing. Currently still in 'work-in-progress' state. Upcoming features: Graphql with Apollo, and mobile responsive design. TechList: JavaScript, Firebase, Stripe, React, React.Saga, React.Hooks, NoSQL, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Styled-Components, Heroku.

#### **GREENthumbsUP** | Demo, Github-Client, Github-Server

A Full-Stack, responsive app where you can create a positive impact on the local restaurant industry by reviewing a place adheres to environment friendly practices. Built using Rest Programming techniques with a PostgreSQL db, Node and Express server and a React Client.

#### **Yoga Track** | Demo, Github-Client, Github-Server

A Full-Stack mobile first responsive app designed for yoga teachers and enthusiasts, helping a user to explore and learn a variety of poses and ability to create class flows. Using Rest Programming techniques this app was built with a PostgreSQL db, Node and Express server and a React Client.

# **EDUCATION**

### THINKFUL | FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

March 2019 - March 2020

1600 + hrs hands on coding experience, mentored by senior developers, agile JavaScript and ES6 - Build interactive client-side web apps with JavaScript, React and jQuery. RESTful APIs with PostgreSQL DB, NodeJS and ExpressJS. Learn modern JWT-based auth flows and test apps with the Mocha and Chai frameworks, and deploy to Heroku and Zeit.

UNIVERSITY OF FINE ARTS | MASTER OF FINE ARTS

2003

# **EXPERIENCE**

# MIRO ART & DESIGN | NORTH SHORE | OWNER

2005 - 2019

Designed and executed a variety of visual solutions for interiors such as murals, custom designed finishes, hand painted furniture and decorative objects. Created art work on commision with consideration of color and style requirements. Assisted and cooperated with interior designers with color and finishes selections. Small business owner experience including: Planning, marketing, estimating, invoicing, accounting, supply ordering and more.

#### E-PRIME SOURCING | SALEM, MA | OPERATIONS MANAGER

2016 - 2018

Oversee office operations: inventory management, pricing, purchase ordering, cloud based accounting, customer invoicing, shipping and receiving.

#### MARKETING BY DESIGN | BEVERLY, MA | INTERN